Griffin Gowdey

Fort Worth, TX 76112 || (239) 919-0174 || gwgowdey@gmail.com || GitHub || LinkedIn

Summary

I am currently a Technical Consultant with <u>HSO ProServ</u> specializing in Microsoft Dynamics 365 CRM/CE. I also am a part-time online student at Tarrant County College studying IT: Programming and an evening part-time virtual Math Tutor with their Northeast Campus Math and Physics Learning Center.

Education/Certifications

Tarrant County College, Remote

Associate of Applied Science in IT: Programming	8/2020 - 8/2021
Level 1 Certificate in Programming	8/2020 - 12/2020
Level 2 Certificate in Programming	1/2021 - 8/2021

Florida State University, Tallahassee, FL

Master of Science in Sport Management

Bachelor of Science in Exercise Physiology

8/2016 - 12/2017
6/2012 - 8/2016

Technical Skills

Software Languages - Python, Java, C++, SQL, R, HTML, and CSS.

Continuing Education - Machine Learning, Computer Vision, JavaScript, and cloud computing.

Professional Experience

HSO ProServ, Remote, Technical Consultant

6/2021 - Present

- Work together with other consultants on the development of client software systems.
- Advise clients on most efficient and effective use of Microsoft Dynamics 365 CRM/CE products.

TCC Northeast Campus Math and Physics Learning Center, Remote, Math Tutor

11/2020 - Present

- Ensure that all visiting students are assisted in a timely and effective manner as they enter.
- Keep up with university math and physics courses and place students with the proper tutor.

Texas Rangers, Arlington, TX/Remote, Support Coordinator, Baseball Systems

1/2020 - 9/2020

- Fixed, coordinated, and followed up with Baseball Systems on open software issues and quality assurance checks.
- Maintained and updated Baseball Operations and software engineering documentation.

Driveline Baseball, Kent, WA, Coordinator of Technical Education

8/2019 - 10/2019

- Worked with High Performance, Hitting, and Pitching staffs to improve software and data collection systems.
- Developed video and written content for coaching certification and new employee education programs.

Driveline Baseball, Kent, WA, Coordinator of Hitting Research

4/2019 - 7/2019

- Proposed new hitting research studies and used existing research to improve hitting development process.
- Assisted Hitting staff with training floor operations and data collection and organization.

Driveline Baseball, Kent, WA, Research and Development Intern

11/2018 - 3/2019

- Collected, cleaned, and analyzed data for assurance of both IRB sponsored and ad-hoc study results.
- Filmed, edited, and organized athlete training video from regular speed, high-speed, and motion capture cameras.

Durham Bulls, Durham, NC, Group Area Host

5/2018 - 10/2018

- Directed companies, organizations, and top-level fans to the specialty areas in the stadium.
- Checked tickets and properly answered any questions from customers or group members.

Houston Astros, Buies Creek, NC, Minor League Technology Apprentice

4/2018 - 9/2018

- Filmed all home games and nearby road games for MiLB affiliate using regular speed and high-speed cameras.
- Implemented new technology initiatives and managed local affiliate technical infrastructure.

Toronto Blue Jays, Dunedin, FL, Coordinator, Spring Training

1/2018 - 3/2018

- Assisted Accounting Manager with payroll reports and employee documentation processing.
- Provided superior customer service to existing and prospective customers in box office and stadium.

FSU Student-Athlete Academic Services, Tallahassee, FL, Educational Services Assistant

9/2017 - 12/2017

- Built student-athlete and tutor scheduling system to improve efficiency of circulation for academic personnel.
- Helped to lead team of over 50 individual student-athlete tutors by designing lesson plans.

Perfect Game, Fort Myers, FL, Scout/Field Manager

6/2017 - 8/2017

- Scored play-by-play of each game and confirmed that games on assigned field started at their listed time.
- Supplied in-depth scouting notes to tournament officials, college coaches, and professional scouts.

FSU Department of Sport Management, Tallahassee, FL, Graduate Teaching Assistant

1/2017 - 5/2017

- Supervised three individual single credit courses and created various lesson plans for each class.
- Instructed 51 total students on the most optimal exercise and learning methods based on their present fitness level.